straightouttasomewhere.com 2015-12-07

# Beats by Dr. Dre | Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to Beats Electronics, LLC. This Privacy Policy is provided to inform you of our policies and practices regarding how we collect, use, disclose, transfer and store information about you.

* ## OUR PRIVACY COMMITMENT

Beats Electronics, LLC and each of its affiliated companies (“ **Beats** ,” “ **we** ,” “ **us** ” or “ **our** ”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of all users of the Beats website where this Privacy Policy is posted (each, a “ **Site** ”) and persons who may contact Beats at our stores and call centers, and through our contests, sweepstakes, and online surveys or use of applications and/or software we may make available from time to time (we refer to the Site, the services made available through the Site, and other services and applications made available by Beats collectively, as the “ **Beats Features** ”). As such, we have established and implemented this Privacy Policy to inform visitors to the Site and users of the Beats Features how we use and protect the information we collect through the Site and the Beats Features. By visiting the Site or using any of the Beats Features, you consent to Beats' collection, use, disclosure, transfer and storage of information relating to you as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

This policy answers the following questions:

  * What information do we collect about you and how do we use it?
  * How do we share your personal information with third parties?
  * How can you access your personal information?
  * What choices do you have about the collection and use of your personal information?
  * That security measures do we take to safeguard your personal information?

* ## WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU AND HOW DO WE USE IT?

**Types of Information We Collect**

Personal information means information that can be used to identify or contact a single person. You may need to submit personal information to access certain aspects of the Site and to access or use certain of the Beats Features.

We collect personal information when you subscribe to the Beats Army (i.e., sign up to receive marketing communications); create a Beats account; participate in feedback forms, product reviews, questionnaires, surveys, contests or sweepstakes; purchase a product through the Beats Features; register a product; request product availability updates; download a software update or application; or receive customer or technical support.

We may collect information from you such as your name, address, zip code, email address, telephone number, language, gender, location information, and date of birth when utilizing the Site and Beats Features. When registering products through the Site we also collect information about your products and where you purchased your products. When you are purchasing products through the Beats Features, you will also be required to provide a billing address and credit card or other payment information. Your credit card and other payment information will not be collected unless you have decided to purchase one of Beats' products.

When you share information and Site links, send or share Beats promotions and marketing materials, or send products to family and friends and others, Beats may collect the information you provide about those people such as name, address, email address and phone number. 

We may also collect information when you register for a Beats account by logging into an account that you already have with certain third-party social networking sites (“SNS”) (including, but not limited to, Facebook and Google+) via our Beats Features. For example, the Beats Features allow you to create an account and login using your Facebook account credentials through Facebook Connect. If you are not currently registered as an account holder on the Site and you click on “Sign in Using Facebook,” you will first be asked to enter your Facebook credentials and then be given the option to register and create a Beats account. We may gather information regarding your SNS profile and other SNS information.

We may combine information you give us with other information from Beats sources, transactions and communications. This may include, but is not limited to, information from Beats retail stores, direct mail, catalogs, events, products and applications or other Beats interactions. We may combine that information with data that is publicly available and data from third parties to personalize your experience and provide communication, content and features matching your profile and interests.

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

The personal information you provide to us will allow us to fulfill your product or service order; alert you of new products or services, features, or enhancements; handle your customer service questions or issues; administer promotions, contests and sweepstakes; register your products; display relevant marketing to you; provide you software and application updates and upgrades; and notify you of promotions, updates, or special offers that we think may interest you. If you have agreed to receive marketing, we also use your email address and phone number as part of the Beats Features in sending you messages about the Beats Features and other general announcements.

We keep track of your interactions with us, including but not limited to your activity within the Beats Features. We may use personal information that you provide to us to send messages to you in response to your request to perform an activity in connection with your use of any of the Beats Features. From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. Because this information is important to your interaction with Beats, you may not opt out of receiving these communications.

If you decide to create your account by logging into a SNS via the Beats Features, you are using the personal information you have already provided to the SNS (such as your “real” name, email address and other information you make publicly available via the SNS) to create your account on our Site; the information we collect may depend on the privacy settings you have with the SNS, so please consult the SNS’s privacy and data practices. For example, by using Facebook Connect, you are allowing Beats to access personal information in your Facebook account pursuant to the Facebook Terms of Use regarding your use of the Beats Features via Facebook.

We may use your personal information that we collect through the Beats Features for analytical and statistical purposes (the “ **Analytical Data** ”). We may use parts of Analytical Data that do not personally identify you for any commercial purpose, including sharing with service providers. We will not sell or trade any part of the Analytical Data that personally identifies any Beats Features users. 

**Cookies and Other Technologies**

Our Site and certain of the Beats Features may use “cookies” and other technologies such as pixel tags and web beacons. These technologies help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of our website people have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. We treat information collected by cookies and other technologies as non-personal information so long as the information cannot be used to identify you. However, to the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we treat these identifiers as personal information.

“Cookies" are small bits of electronic information that a website sends to a visitor's browser and are stored on the visitor's hard drive. Like many websites, we employ cookies and other technologies in certain areas of the Site to allow us to provide information to make your online experience more convenient. For example, when you return to the Site after logging in, cookies provide information to the Site so that the Site will remember who you are on subsequent visits, speeding up or enhancing your experience of the Beats Features by, for instance, tailoring content to you. Cookies also prevent items placed in a shopping basket from disappearing by the time you checkout. Beats and our partners also use cookies and other technologies to remember personal information when you use our Beats Features.

If you want to disable cookies on your web browser through your browser settings, please consult your browser’s help menu for assistance. Please note that certain Beats Features will not be available once cookies are disabled.

In some of our email messages, we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Site. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our website. We track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages.

A pixel tag or web beacon is an often-transparent graphic image, usually no larger than 1 pixel by 1 pixel, that is placed on a website or in an email that is used to monitor the behavior of the user visiting the website or sending the email. We may use web beacons and/or pixel tags for many purposes, including site usage analytics, advertising, auditing and reporting, and content and advertising personalization. 

**Targeted Advertising**

Beats and our partners use cookies and other technologies to remember personal information about your visits to our Site and other websites to control the number of times you see a given ad, deliver ads that relate to your interests, and measure the effectiveness of ad campaigns. If you do not want to receive ads with this level of relevance, you can opt out by clicking [here](http://preferences.truste.com/). If you opt out, you will continue to receive the same number of ads, but they may be less relevant because they will not be based on your interests. You may still see ads related to the content on a web page or based on other non-personal information. 

**Information Collected Automatically**

Our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit the Site. This information includes your Internet Protocol address, your browser type and version, the search engine you used to find the Beats Features, if any, referring and exit pages, date/time stamp and clickstream data, which Beats Features you use and when and how long you use them. We use this information to monitor and analyze how users use the Beats Features, to provide customer service, to maintain and improve the Beats Features, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may use this information in our marketing and advertising services.

We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”) to collect certain information relating to your use of the Site. Google uses cookies to collect and process data about your use of the Site. For more information regarding how Google uses data when you use our Site, please visit www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/.

**Children's Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under the age of 13, we will delete the information as soon as possible. We take children's privacy seriously, and encourage parents to play an active role in their children's online experience at all times. 

* ## HOW DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES?

**Sharing of Information**

Except as described in this policy, or with your consent, we will not share your personal information with third parties. We use your personal information to complete transactions, respond to your requests, deliver products and services you request, and send communications to you about promotions, updates, or special offers (which may be offered by Beats or one of its business partners) that may be of interest to you. We may share your personal information with service providers, including companies that perform marketing services and other business operations for us. We may also share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information with prospective partners and other third parties.

In addition, we will share the personal information we collect from you under the following circumstances:

  * Legal requests or protection of rights. We will share personal information if we have a good faith belief that (i) access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, such as a court order or subpoena, or a request by law enforcement or governmental authorities, (ii) such action is appropriate to enforce our [Terms of Use](http://www.beatsbydre.com/support/terms-of-use.html) for the Beats Features, including any investigation of potential violations thereof, (iii) such action is necessary to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues associated with the Beats Features, or (iv) such action is appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of Beats, its employees, users of the Beats Features or others.
  * Asset transfers. If we become involved in a merger, acquisition or other transaction involving the sale of some or all of Beats' assets, user information, including personal information collected from you through your use of the Beats Features, could be included in the transferred assets. Should such an event occur, we will use reasonable means to notify you through email and/or a prominent notice on the Site.
  * Service Providers. We may share your personal information with service providers that we engage for the purpose of processing information on our and your behalf. For example, we may partner with other companies to process payments for the Beats Features. Additionally, we may partner with other companies to process, supplement, analyze, and/or store data, including, but not limited to, Analytical Data. While providing services for us, these companies may access your personal information. To the extent applicable, we require these entities to comply with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * Social Networking Sites. We may share the information in your account (including your personal information) with the SNSs that you have linked to your account. These third parties have access to your personal information only for this purpose (unless the SNS has received your personal information independently of the Beats Features) and not for other purposes. We allow users to link their Facebook accounts and Google+ accounts to the Beats Features. Users may be able to post recent activity through the Beats Features back to their SNS account. You will be prompted to decide whether or not your activity through the Beats Features will be shared and disclosed on your SNS service.

**Additional Information You Should Know About Third Parties**

This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of third party websites linked to the Site. Although we encourage such third parties to adopt and follow their own privacy policies, we are not responsible for their collection and use of your personal information. You should refer to the privacy policies and statements of other websites or contact the respective webmasters of those websites to obtain information regarding their information collection, use and disclosure policies.

When you have clicked on a third party logo or URL displayed on our Site which links you to a different website, our Privacy Policy no longer applies and you must read the privacy policy of the third party to see how your personal information will be handled on their website.

* ## HOW CAN YOU ACCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

You can access the personal information we have relating to your online account by visiting the [My Account](https://www.beatsbydre.com/account) section of our Site. You can access other personal information we have collected from you through our Site by sending us an email [here](https://www.beatsbydre.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-beats-Site/en_US/CustomerService-ContactUs).

* ## WHAT CHOICES DO YOU HAVE ABOUT THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

**Control of Your Information**

You can change certain personal information we have about you by going to the [My Account](https://www.beatsbydre.com/account) section of our Site. You may also request us to change or delete any information you've shared with use by sending us an email [here](https://www.beatsbydre.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-beats-Site/en_US/CustomerService-ContactUs). We will retain certain information to prevent fraud, and for customer and order management purposes, to enforce our agreements, and as otherwise required or permitted by law. 

**Opting Out of Receiving Communications from Us**

If you no longer want to receive our newsletter, emails or other announcements, you may unsubscribe by sending us an email [here](https://www.beatsbydre.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-beats-Site/en_US/CustomerService-ContactUs) or replying to the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our emails. Please note that you cannot unsubscribe from certain correspondence from us, including messages relating to your transactions.

**Mediation**

If you are a resident of a country outside of the European Union, you also agree that, in the event any dispute or claim arises out of or relating to this Privacy Policy that you and Beats will attempt in good faith to negotiate a written resolution of the matter directly between the parties. You agree that if the matter remains unresolved for forty-five (45) days after notification (via certified mail or personal delivery) that a dispute exists, all parties shall join in mediation services in Los Angeles, California with a mutually agreed mediator in an attempt to resolve the dispute. Should you file any arbitration claims, or any administrative or legal actions without first having attempted to resolve the matter by mediation, then you agree that you will not be entitled to recover attorneys' fees, even if you would otherwise be entitled to them.

**Dispute Resolution for Residents of the European Union**

If you are a resident of the European Union, in the event that you have any dispute or claim arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy, you may report your claim to the European Union Data Protection Authorities located in your jurisdiction.

* ## WHAT SECURITY MEASURES DO WE TAKE TO SAFEGUARD YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

The personal information that you provide to us is stored on servers, which are located in secured facilities with restricted access, and protected by protocols and procedures designed to ensure the security of such information. In addition, we restrict access to personal information to Beats employees, independent contractors and agents who need to know this information in order to develop, operate and maintain the Beats Features. All Beats personnel who have access to this information are trained in the maintenance and security of such information. However, no server, computer or communications network or system, or data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect user information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or through the use of any of the Beats Features and you acknowledge and agree that you provide such information and engage in such transmissions at your own risk. Once we receive a transmission from you, we will endeavour to maintain its security on our systems. 

* ## INTERNATIONAL USERS

All the information you provide may be transferred or accessed by entities around the world as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Beats complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework that was established by the U.S. Department of Commerce in consultation with the European Commission to comply with the European Commission's Directive on Data Protection. Beats also complies with the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework that was established by the U.S. Department of Commerce in consultation with the Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner of Switzerland to comply with the Swiss Federal Act on Data Protection. Beats has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Beats’ certification, please see the Apple Inc. certification at <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

* ## NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If we make a material change we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. 

* ## QUESTIONS? CONTACT US

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy, please contact us by emailing [here](https://www.beatsbydre.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-beats-Site/en_US/CustomerService-ContactUs). You can also contact us by phone using the support number for your country listed [here](http://www.beatsbydre.com/support/international-numbers.html). 

* ## TERMS OF USE

Please read the [Terms of Use](http://www.beatsbydre.com/support/terms-of-use.html) governing the use of the Site and the Beats Features.
